mariio128.com 2012-12-30

# HELP CENTER :: PRIVACY POLICY - MARIIO128 GAMES & ENTERTAINMENT

**Privacy Policy**  
MARIIO128.com respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the information we collect from you.  

**Personal Information**  
This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you register and set up an account, order a product or service.  
   
**Collecting Your Information**  
Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

The type of information we may collect about you includes:

  * Your name
  * Your address
  * Your email address
  * Your phone number
  * Your order history and profile

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. We do not collect or store your bank details, credit or debit card information in any form.

When you agree to pay for your items by credit card, you are redirected to secure pages hosted on the web servers managed by payment gateways i.e. Paypal. Payment gateways authenticate and process your card. Once your card has been charged, you are redirected back to our website.  

**How We Use Your Infomration**  
We collect your information in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials( if you have successfully subscribed for any).

Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contained and these changes will be automatically kept for future use. We may require additional verifications or information before accepting any order.

We DO NOT share or sell your information with any third parties. You will only be contacted by us to confirm your order status, to respond to your enquiry.  

**Protecting Your Privacy**  
  
We are committed to protecting your privacy, therefore we have strict security measures in place to protect the information you provide us with. 

We use the latest 258-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is collected.

To make purchases from us, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Firefox, or Internet Explorer. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

When you submit product reviews or messages on social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. You will be responsible for all activities and orders submitted under your login and password.  

**Cookies**  
  
A "cookie" is a small piece of data that is stored on your web browser or hard disk by a web server. This data usually contains encoded information that informs the web server how and when you used the site. Cookies are commonly used on the Internet and do not harm your computer system.

The cookies used on this site do not include any information that others could read and understand about you, such as your name or any login or order details. They contain no Personal Information about you.

Because cookies allow you to have the benefit of our personalized features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. You must have cookies enabled in order to checkout on our website.  

**Third Party Websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

If you decide to provide Personal Information to any third party website linked from one of our Websites, the sharing of such information will be subject to the privacy policy of that company, not our privacy practices. Be cautious before providing any Personal Information to any third party.  

**Children Privacy**  
You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 18 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us so that we may delete the child's information.  
   
**Policy Update**  
We may make changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.
